thevid.tv 2019-05-02

# TheVid

Your privacy is important to TheVid. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that TheVid collects, and the ways in which TheVid uses that personal information. 

## Personal information collection

TheVid may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: 

  * \- information about your use of this website (including uploaded videos);
  * \- information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including Facebook® account ID and e-mail address);
  * \- any other information that you send to TheVid.

## Using personal information

TheVid may use your personal information to: 

  * \- administer this website;
  * \- personalize the website for you;
  * \- enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * \- publish information about you on the website;
  * \- send to you products that you purchase;
  * \- supply to you services that you purchase;
  * \- send to you statements and invoices;
  * \- collect payments from you; 
  * \- send you marketing communications.

Your private information will be also shared when the following conditions are met: 

  * \- (a) User uploads prohibited content (See Terms and Conditions for Definition); 
  * \- (b) User exploits TheVid for illegitimate purposes;
  * \- (c) User used stolen payment credentials

Any of the following nullify our privacy obligations towards the user, which can result in sharing of your private information with a 3rd party.

TheVid discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. 

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, TheVid may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. 

## Securing your data

TheVid will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

TheVid will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure servers].

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.] 

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that TheVid collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which TheVid operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information. 

## Updating this statement

TheVid may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

## Contact TheVid

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or TheVid's treatment of your personal information, please contact us.
